<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>News &#8211; Connect Pwc</title>
	<atom:link href="https://connect.pwc.ch/category/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://connect.pwc.ch</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 19:57:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>A user revealed the first flaw in Tesla&#8217;s Cyber Truck</title>
		<link>https://connect.pwc.ch/a-user-revealed-the-first-flaw-in-teslas-cyber-truck/</link>
					<comments>https://connect.pwc.ch/a-user-revealed-the-first-flaw-in-teslas-cyber-truck/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 19:57:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://connect.pwc.ch/?p=30</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[There is a lot of curiosity in the technology world about the cyber truck made by Tesla, an electric car manufacturer owned by Elon Musk. Tesla delivered 10 to 12 Cyber Trucks to customers for the first time on November 30. And so many car lovers are interested to know the various technical aspects of ... <a title="A user revealed the first flaw in Tesla&#8217;s Cyber Truck" class="read-more" href="https://connect.pwc.ch/a-user-revealed-the-first-flaw-in-teslas-cyber-truck/" aria-label="More on A user revealed the first flaw in Tesla&#8217;s Cyber Truck">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>There is a lot of curiosity in the technology world about the cyber truck made by Tesla, an electric car manufacturer owned by Elon Musk. Tesla delivered 10 to 12 Cyber Trucks to customers for the first time on November 30. And so many car lovers are interested to know the various technical aspects of this electric-powered pickup. However, within a month and a half of entering the market, errors were found in the design and signal control of the Cyber Truck. A person named &#8216;Nan&#8217; identified these errors in the cyber truck.</p>



<p>After driving for about 80 km, Nan noticed these defects of the cyber truck. He said that some of the panels on the exterior of the Cyber Truck on the side of the truck bed have positional anomalies. Apart from this, the right side signal control of the vehicle is also defective. Despite these defects, he expressed his satisfaction with the steering and acceleration of the Cyber Truck.</p>



<p>Made of stainless steel, the Cyber Truck has a 6-feet long and 4-feet wide space for transporting goods. The car can carry 25 thousand pounds. Apart from this, the towing capacity of the car is 11 thousand pounds. Due to the stainless steel body, the car does not stain or scratch, so painting is not required. More than two million people have already registered to buy the Tesla-made Cyber Truck. Depending on the model and version, the price of Cyber Truck is 60 thousand 990, 79 thousand 990 and 99 thousand 990 US dollars.</p>



<p>It should be noted that on December 28, a cyber truck was involved in an accident on Skyline Boulevard in Palo Alto, California, USA. At that time, the cyber truck collided with a Toyota Corolla car. While the Toyota car was damaged in the accident, the Cyber truck was not damaged.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://connect.pwc.ch/a-user-revealed-the-first-flaw-in-teslas-cyber-truck/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Wozniacki sees &#8216;opportunity for change&#8217; in Saudi Arabia</title>
		<link>https://connect.pwc.ch/wozniacki-sees-opportunity-for-change-in-saudi-arabia/</link>
					<comments>https://connect.pwc.ch/wozniacki-sees-opportunity-for-change-in-saudi-arabia/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 19:54:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://connect.pwc.ch/?p=27</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Rafael Nadal has become the ambassador of the country&#8217;s tennis federation as part of the special importance given to sports in Saudi Crown Prince Mohammed bin Salman&#8217;s &#8216;Vision 2030&#8217; reform project. Nadal will visit Saudi every year as an ambassador. Besides helping the development of tennis, he will also monitor the progress of the academy. ... <a title="Wozniacki sees &#8216;opportunity for change&#8217; in Saudi Arabia" class="read-more" href="https://connect.pwc.ch/wozniacki-sees-opportunity-for-change-in-saudi-arabia/" aria-label="More on Wozniacki sees &#8216;opportunity for change&#8217; in Saudi Arabia">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Rafael Nadal has become the ambassador of the country&#8217;s tennis federation as part of the special importance given to sports in Saudi Crown Prince Mohammed bin Salman&#8217;s &#8216;Vision 2030&#8217; reform project. Nadal will visit Saudi every year as an ambassador. Besides helping the development of tennis, he will also monitor the progress of the academy.</p>



<p>After becoming the ambassador of the Saudi Tennis Federation yesterday, Nadal said, &#8216;I want this game to spread globally. Saudi Arabia is a really promising country in this field. Australian Open winner Caroline Wozniacki also believes that there is an opportunity for positive changes in the country&#8217;s tennis through the hands of star tennis players.</p>



<p>Wozniacki returned to the Australian Open after 4 years due to the birth of two children and maternity responsibilities. The 33-year-old Danish tennis star&#8217;s return has not been pleasant. Today the young Russian lost to Maria Timofeeva and was eliminated from the second round.</p>



<p>At the press conference after the match, Wozniacki said about Nadal being the ambassador of Saudi tennis, &#8216;I haven&#8217;t read much about Rafa (Nadal), what he is actually doing. But clearly he is asserting his strong position in Saudi sports. First golf and football and now tennis.</p>



<p>Wozniacki believes that Saudi Arabia is developing a strong position in sports, &#8220;I think it&#8217;s inevitable, it&#8217;s going to happen.&#8221; When that happens, there is an opportunity for us to make a difference and do something good.&#8217;</p>



<p>The developed world has been vocal about human rights violations in Saudi Arabia for a long time. Critics believe that in order to improve its image in the international arena, Saudi Arabia must stop its anti-humanitarian activities. This attempt to use sports to increase Saudi&#8217;s international reputation is nothing more than &#8216;sports washing&#8217; in the eyes of critics.</p>



<p>However, Wozniacki believes that positive changes will be made in Saudi sports by the hand of star players, &#8220;I understand human rights and other issues. But I think with the amount of money they (Saudi Arabia) are pouring into sports, it&#8217;s inevitable. We have an opportunity to change (the perception of Saudi) by doing something good.</p>



<p>The Saudi Tennis Federation hosted the Next Gen ATP Finals in Jeddah last November-December. In addition, there were two exhibition matches between Novak Djokovic-Carlos Alcaraz and Ariana Sabalenka-Unus Jabir. It is heard that Saudi will also host the WTI Finals this year.</p>



<p>But the matter is not so clear for Iga Seontek, who is at the top of the women&#8217;s tennis rankings. The 22-year-old Polish star said, &#8216;The WTA Finals are going to be in Saudi &#8211; I&#8217;ve heard a lot of rumours. We are still waiting for the decision. Whether it&#8217;s good or not, it&#8217;s always hard for me to say. Because, in that area (Arab world) it is not easy for girls to play sports. But it is true that those countries want to progress politically and socially.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://connect.pwc.ch/wozniacki-sees-opportunity-for-change-in-saudi-arabia/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Two US Navy SEALs commandos are missing in an operation to seize arms from the Houthis</title>
		<link>https://connect.pwc.ch/two-us-navy-seals-commandos-are-missing-in-an-operation-to-seize-arms-from-the-houthis/</link>
					<comments>https://connect.pwc.ch/two-us-navy-seals-commandos-are-missing-in-an-operation-to-seize-arms-from-the-houthis/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 19:50:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://connect.pwc.ch/?p=24</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Two US Navy SEAL commandos have gone missing during an operation to seize a shipment of Iranian-made weapons en route to Yemen&#8217;s Houthi rebels. The United States military said this information. The US military&#8217;s Central Command (CENTCOM) said in a statement on Tuesday that Navy SEALs conducted the operation in the international waters of the ... <a title="Two US Navy SEALs commandos are missing in an operation to seize arms from the Houthis" class="read-more" href="https://connect.pwc.ch/two-us-navy-seals-commandos-are-missing-in-an-operation-to-seize-arms-from-the-houthis/" aria-label="More on Two US Navy SEALs commandos are missing in an operation to seize arms from the Houthis">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Two US Navy SEAL commandos have gone missing during an operation to seize a shipment of Iranian-made weapons en route to Yemen&#8217;s Houthi rebels. The United States military said this information.</p>



<p>The US military&#8217;s Central Command (CENTCOM) said in a statement on Tuesday that Navy SEALs conducted the operation in the international waters of the Arabian Sea near the coast of Somalia on Thursday night.</p>



<p>A CENTCOM statement said the operation led to the seizure of Iranian-made missile parts and other weapons en route to the Houthis. A small boat carrying these weapons was also seized.</p>



<p>Although the operation was carried out last Thursday, two commandos of the Navy SEALs have now been reported missing. Navy SEALs are a special operations unit of the US Navy.</p>



<p>According to CENTCOM, these two commandos of the Navy SEALs were involved in the operation conducted near the coast of Somalia last Thursday.</p>



<p>US media reports citing US defense officials said Navy SEALs commandos went to the scene in small special operations craft. A commando of the Navy SEALs was thrown into the sea by a huge wave while boarding the gunboat. Another commando of the Navy Seals went into the sea to rescue him. Both commandos are still missing.</p>



<p>CENTCOM Commander General Michael Eric Kurilla said they are conducting a massive search for their missing colleagues.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://connect.pwc.ch/two-us-navy-seals-commandos-are-missing-in-an-operation-to-seize-arms-from-the-houthis/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Russian schoolgirl&#8217;s surprise defeating the sixth seed in the Australian Open</title>
		<link>https://connect.pwc.ch/russian-schoolgirls-surprise-defeating-the-sixth-seed-in-the-australian-open/</link>
					<comments>https://connect.pwc.ch/russian-schoolgirls-surprise-defeating-the-sixth-seed-in-the-australian-open/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 19:46:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://connect.pwc.ch/?p=21</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[&#8220;It seems that I am more mature now than before.&#8221;&#8220;You&#8217;re only 16.&#8221;&#8216;Yes, but last year there were 15.&#8217; Rod Laver Arena laughed at Mira Andreeva&#8217;s conversation with the referee after the match. A year ago Andriva cried after losing in the final of the girls category. This time he himself, the audience was also laughing ... <a title="Russian schoolgirl&#8217;s surprise defeating the sixth seed in the Australian Open" class="read-more" href="https://connect.pwc.ch/russian-schoolgirls-surprise-defeating-the-sixth-seed-in-the-australian-open/" aria-label="More on Russian schoolgirl&#8217;s surprise defeating the sixth seed in the Australian Open">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>&#8220;It seems that I am more mature now than before.&#8221;<br>&#8220;You&#8217;re only 16.&#8221;<br>&#8216;Yes, but last year there were 15.&#8217;</p>



<p>Rod Laver Arena laughed at Mira Andreeva&#8217;s conversation with the referee after the match.</p>



<p>A year ago Andriva cried after losing in the final of the girls category. This time he himself, the audience was also laughing after giving birth to a surprise in the second round of women&#8217;s singles. The 16-year-old schoolgirl from Russia lost to her ideal Tunisian Uns Jabir, who is seeded sixth in the tournament. That too in a 6-0, 6-2 game in less than an hour. This is Andreeva&#8217;s first win against someone ranked in the top 10.</p>



<p>After the win Andriva said about playing without pressure, &#8216;I was really nervous before the match, but I saw he was nervous too. It helped me, because I realized I&#8217;m not the only one nervous before a match. I just wanted to enjoy, because it&#8217;s Rod Laver Arena, playing against someone I love. I just wanted to play and I think I played well.&#8217;</p>



<p>This is only Andreeva&#8217;s second match on Center Court in Melbourne. She lost to compatriot Alina Korniva in the girls&#8217; final last year. Andreeva, who was &#8220;very disappointed&#8221; with the loss, says that the match helped her to move forward. After the match, he said, &#8220;Today when I saw that I will play Rod Laver, I said to myself &#8211; this time I have to take a chance.&#8221; Must win first time on big court. I won.</p>



<p>Andriva also says that this is the best match in his career, &#8216;I did not expect to play so well in the first set. The second set wasn&#8217;t bad either. Yes, it was a great match for me.</p>



<p>Andreeva will face France&#8217;s Diane Parry in the next round. However, this is not the first Grand Slam for him. Last year, he reached the third round at the French Open and the fourth round at Wimbledon after getting past the qualifiers. However, he lost in the second round to eventual champion Coco Goff at the US Open. Andreeva dreams of a tennis career, but she also has to deal with school. He said, &#8216;I have to do a lot at school. In fact, it started two days ago, so I have to go. Then he added, &#8220;I don&#8217;t like chemistry.&#8221;</p>



<p>Andreeva is so young, how many tournaments she can play in, that has also been fixed by the WTA. Andriva, who is now number 47, doesn&#8217;t want to think about how much she can go up in the ranking, &#8216;I mean, I am 16 now. Why should you think about ranking? I am climbing higher and my goal is to climb higher. Maybe a little, but high. I don&#8217;t know exactly. I try not to think about these things. I want to think only about tennis.</p>



<p>Jabir was defeated by Andreeva today in just 20 minutes. The 29-year-old Jabir from Tunisia was not in the rhythm at all today. Scored just eight points in six games, including just three from the baseline. The runner-up in three Grand Slams made 10 unforced errors today.</p>



<p>Andrivar&#8217;s victory today at the Australian Open is not the only &#8216;Russian-shock&#8217;. 2018 champion Caroline Wozniacki lost to 20-year-old Maria Timofeva of Russia. After losing the first set 6-1, Timofeva came back in style, winning the next two sets 6-4, 6-1.</p>



<p>Timofeva said after the match, &#8220;It was an honor to play here today against Caroline.&#8221; I can&#8217;t express how happy I am, I could ask for more than that.&#8217;</p>



<p>Timofeva&#8217;s opponent in the next round is tenth seed Beatriz Haddad Maia of Brazil.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://connect.pwc.ch/russian-schoolgirls-surprise-defeating-the-sixth-seed-in-the-australian-open/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The electric-powered pickup is made by Vietnam&#8217;s Vinfast</title>
		<link>https://connect.pwc.ch/the-electric-powered-pickup-is-made-by-vietnams-vinfast/</link>
					<comments>https://connect.pwc.ch/the-electric-powered-pickup-is-made-by-vietnams-vinfast/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 19:41:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://connect.pwc.ch/?p=18</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[There is a lot of curiosity in the technology world about the electric-powered pickup &#8216;Cyber Truck&#8217; made by Tesla, the electric car manufacturer owned by Elon Musk. This time, the Vietnamese car manufacturer Vinfast has developed an electric-powered pickup named &#8216;VF Wild&#8217;. The company also showcased its electric-powered pickup at the Consumer Electronics Show in ... <a title="The electric-powered pickup is made by Vietnam&#8217;s Vinfast" class="read-more" href="https://connect.pwc.ch/the-electric-powered-pickup-is-made-by-vietnams-vinfast/" aria-label="More on The electric-powered pickup is made by Vietnam&#8217;s Vinfast">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>There is a lot of curiosity in the technology world about the electric-powered pickup &#8216;Cyber Truck&#8217; made by Tesla, the electric car manufacturer owned by Elon Musk. This time, the Vietnamese car manufacturer Vinfast has developed an electric-powered pickup named &#8216;VF Wild&#8217;. The company also showcased its electric-powered pickup at the Consumer Electronics Show in the United States.</p>



<p>Named VF Wild, the electric pickup has four doors, two rows of seating and a five-foot-long cargo bed. The passenger seat of the pickup can be folded inward when needed. As a result, it is possible to carry more than three feet of cargo in addition to the cargo bed.</p>



<p>According to Vinfast, the VF Wild pickup was originally developed as an electric-powered pickup prototype. Future electric-powered pickups will follow this example. The pickup is not considered a rival to Tesla&#8217;s Cyber Truck due to its smaller size.</p>



<p>Apart from the VF Wild, Vinfast also showcased an electric SUV called the VF 3. The car is available in Vietnam and will soon go on sale in the US market. This two-door electric SUV is compact in size. The car can travel 125 miles on a single charge.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://connect.pwc.ch/the-electric-powered-pickup-is-made-by-vietnams-vinfast/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
